CONTACT

- (+57) 300 322 3023
- kcomtdaniel@gmail.com
- Github
- Linkedin
- <u>Instagram</u>
- <u>Portfolio</u>

LANGUAGES

- CSS₃
- HTML5
- Javascript
- Typescript
- NodeJS
- SQL

FRAMEWORKS & LIBRARIES

- ReactJS
- Tailwind
- SliderJS
- Bootstrap

SOFT SKILLS

- Team work
- Asertive communication
- Problem solving mindset

EDUCATION

Universidad Monteávila. Cum Laude in Social Communication.

HOBBIES

- Salsa and Bachata Dancing
- Creating Audiovisual Content
- Trekking

ABOUT ME

I am a passionate and adaptable professional who enjoys creating amazing user experiences and tackling technical challenges. I have taught myself frontend development using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and ReactJS, one of the most popular frameworks in the industry. I have more than six months of experience developing with ReactJS and using tools like Chrome DevTools to debug and optimize my code.

I also have skills in communication, radio and TV production, audio-visual specialization, and project management. I have a professional working proficiency in English and can use systems like Notion, HubSpot, Go High Level and Slack. I am open-minded, detail-oriented, responsible, and confident. I can work independently or in a team, meet deadlines, and learn from others.

WORK EXPERIENCE

• React Web Developer

2023 (Current)

Freelance. Developed Personal Projects such as the frontend side of https://thexo.encolados.com: a multiplayer game of Tic Tac Toe collaborating with a backend developer. Website building.

Tech Support Specialist

On The Fuze 2022-2023

Responsible for onboarding clients and tech support. Used CRM GoHighLevel and Hubspot. Analyzed user experience with Hotjar and Google Analytics and optimized Landing Pages.

Wordpress Web Developer

2020-2022

Freelance. Created Landing Pages and Websites for individuals using plugins such as Elementor Pro with Wordpress. Filmed and edited videos and executed marketing strategies.

COURSES

Harvard University (2022)

• CS50: Introduction to Computer Science

Platzi (2022 - 2023)

- Pensamiento Lógico: Manejo de Datos, Estructuras y Funciones.
- Curso Definitivo de HTML y CSS.
- Curso Práctico de JavaScript
- Curso de Frontend Developer
- Frontend con React.js